fatforweightloss.com.au 2019-04-22

# Privacy Policy - FatForWeightLoss

This privacy policy sets out how FatForWeightLoss uses and protects any information that you give while using [https://www.fatforweightloss.com.au](https://www.fatforweightloss.com.au/)

Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

FatForWeightLoss may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 25/01/2017.

 **What we collect**

We may collect the following information:

  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as zip code, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

 **What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

 **Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

 **How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

 **Advertising**

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and Service Provider disclaims all liability in connection therewith.

 **Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

 **Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting us.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

 **Opt Out**

For information about opting out of Gourmet Ads and ad serving partners please visit 

<https://www.adthrive.com/adthrive-privacy-statement/>

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact me.

GDPR  
FatForWeightLoss

## 1\. We respect your privacy

1.1. FatForWeightLoss respects your right to privacy and is committed to safeguarding the privacy of our customers and website visitors. This policy sets out how we collect and treat your personal information.  
1.2. We adhere to the Australian Privacy Principles contained in the Privacy Act 1988(Cth) and to the extent applicable, the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).  
1.3. “Personal information” is information we hold which is identifiable as being about you. This includes information such as your name, email address, identification number, or any other type of information that can reasonably identify an individual, either directly or indirectly.  
1.4. You may contact us in writing at Parcel Locker 10009 92368 75-77 Russell Street, West End, Queensland, 4101 for further information about this Privacy Policy.

## 2\. What personal information is collected

2.1. FatForWeightLoss will, from time to time, receive and store personal information you submit to our website, provided to us directly or given to us in other forms.

2.2. You may provide basic information such as your name, phone number, address and email address to enable us to send you information, provide updates and process your product or service order.  
2.3. We may collect additional information at other times, including but not limited to, when you provide feedback, when you provide information about your personal or business affairs, change your content or email preference, respond to surveys and/or promotions, provide financial or credit card information, or communicate with our customer support.  
2.4. Additionally, we may also collect any other information you provide while interacting with us.

## 3\. How we collect your personal information

3.1. FatForWeightLoss collects personal information from you in a variety of ways, including when you interact with us electronically or in person, when you access our website and when we engage in business activities with you. We may receive personal information from third parties. If we do, we will protect it as set out in  
this Privacy Policy.  
3.2. By providing us with personal information, you consent to the supply of that information subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

## 4\. How we use your personal information

4.1. FatForWeightLoss may use personal information collected from you to provide you with information about our products or services. We may also make you If you withhold your personal information, it may not be possible for us to provide you with our products and services or for you to fully access our website.  
aware of new and additional products, services and opportunities available to you.  
4.2. FatForWeightLoss will use personal information only for the purposes that you consent to. This may include to:  
(a) provide you with products and services during the usual course of our business  
activities;  
(b) administer our business activities;  
(c) manage, research and develop our products and services;  
(d) provide you with information about our products and services;  
(e) communicate with you by a variety of measures including, but not limited to, by  
telephone, email,sms or mail; and  
(f) investigate any complaints.  
4.3. We may disclose your personal information to comply with a legal requirement, such as a law, regulation, court order, subpoena, warrant, legal proceedings or in response to a law enforcement agency request.

4.4. If there is a change of control in our business or a sale or transfer of business assets, we reserve the right to transfer to the extent permissible at law our user databases, together with any personal information and non-personal information contained in those databases.

## 5\. Disclosure of your personal information

5.1. FatForWeightLoss may disclose your personal information to any of our employees, officers, insurers, professional advisers, agents, suppliers or ubcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy policy.  
5.2. If we do disclose your personal information to a third party, we will protect it in accordance with this privacy policy.

## 6\. General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) for the European Union (EU)

6.1. FatForWeightLoss will comply with the principles of data protection set out in the GDPR for the purpose of fairness, transparency and lawful data collection and use.  
6.2. We process your personal information as a Processor and/or to the extent that we are a Controller as defined in the GDPR.  
6.3. We must establish a lawful basis for processing your personal information. The legal basis for which we collect your personal information depends on the data that we collect and how we use it.  
6.4. We will only collect your personal information with your express consent for a specific purpose and any data collected will be to the extent necessary and not excessive for its purpose. We will keep your data safe and secure.  
6.5. We will also process your personal information if it is necessary for our legitimate interests, or to fulfil a contractual or legal obligation.  
6.6. We process your personal information if it is necessary to protect your life or in a medical situation, it is necessary to carry out a public function, a task of public interest or if the function has a clear basis in law.  
6.7. We do not collect or process any personal information from you that is considered “Sensitive Personal Information” under the GDPR, such as personal information relating to your sexual orientation or ethnic origin unless we have  
obtained your explicit consent, or if it is being collected subject to and in accordance with the GDPR.  
6.8. You must not provide us with your personal information if you are under the age of 16 without the consent of your parent or someone who has parental authority for you. We do not knowingly collect or process the personal information of  
children.

## 7\. Your rights under the GDPR

7.1. If you are an individual residing in the EU, you have certain rights as to how your personal information is obtained and used. FatForWeightLoss complies with your rights under the GDPR as to how your personal information is used and controlled if you are an individual residing in the EU  
7.2. Except as otherwise provided in the GDPR, you have the following rights:  
(a) to be informed how your personal information is being used;  
(b) access your personal information (we will provide you with a free copy of it);  
(c) to correct your personal information if it is inaccurate or incomplete;  
(d) to delete your personal information (also known as “the right to be forgotten”);  
(e) to restrict the processing of your personal information;  
(f) to retain and reuse your personal information for your own purposes;  
(g) to object to your personal information being used; and  
(h) to object against automated decision making and profiling.  
7.3. Please contact us at any time to exercise your rights under the GDPR at the contact details in this Privacy Policy.  
7.4. We may ask you to verify your identity before acting on any of your requests.

## 8\. Hosting and International Data Transfers

8.1. Information that we collect may from time to time be stored, processed in or transferred between parties or sites located in countries outside of Australia. These may include, but are not limited to Australia.8.2. We and our other group companies have offices and/or facilities in Australia. Transfers to each of these countries will be protected by appropriate safeguards, these include one or more of the following: the use of standard data protection clauses adopted or approved by the European Commission which you can obtain from the European Commission Website; the use of binding corporate rules, a copy of which you can obtain from FatForWeightloss the European Commission Website; the use of binding corporate rules, a copy of which you can obtain from FatForWeightLoss’s Data Protection Officer.  
8.4. Our Suppliers and Contractors are situated in Australia. Transfers to each of these Countries will be protected by appropriate safeguards, these include one or more of the following: the use of standard data protection clauses adopted or approved by the European Commission which you can obtain from the European Commission Website; the use of binding corporate rules, a copy of which you can obtain from FatForWeightLoss’s Data Protection Officer.  
8.5. You acknowledge that personal data that you submit for publication through our website or services may be available, via the internet, around the world. We cannot prevent the use (or misuse) of such personal data by others.

## 9\. Security of your personal information

9.1. FatForWeightLoss is committed to ensuring that the information you provide to us is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure information and protect it from misuse, interference, loss  and unauthorised access, modification and disclosure.  
9.2. Where we employ data processors to process personal information on our behalf, we only do so on the basis that such data processors comply with the requirements under the GDPR and that have adequate technical measures in place to protect personal information against unauthorised use, loss and theft.  
9.3. The transmission and exchange of information is carried out at your own risk. We cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to us, or receive from us. Although we take measures to safeguard against unauthoriseddisclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personal information that  
we collect will not be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

## 10\. Access to your personal information

10.1. You may request details of personal information that we hold about you in accordance with the provisions of the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth), and to the extent applicable the EU GDPR. If you would like a copy of the information which we hold about you or believe that any information we hold on you is inaccurate, out  
of date, incomplete, irrelevant or misleading, please email us at admin@fatforweightloss.com.au.  
10.2. We reserve the right to refuse to provide you with information that we hold about you, in certain circumstances set out in the Privacy Act or any other applicable law.

## 11\. Complaints about privacy

11.1. If you have any complaints about our privacy practices, please feel free to sendin details of your complaints to admin@fatforweightloss.com.au. We take  complaints very seriously and will respond shortly after receiving written notice of your complaint. 1st June 2018

## 12\. Changes to Privacy Policy

12.1. Please be aware that we may change this Privacy Policy in the future. We may modify this Policy at any time, in our sole discretion and all modifications will be  effective immediately upon our posting of the modifications on our website or notice board. Please check back from time to time to review our Privacy Policy.

## 13\. Website

13.1. When you visit our website When you come to our website (https://www.fatforweightloss.com.au), we may collect certain information such as browser type, operating system, website visited immediately before coming to our site, etc. This information is used in an aggregated manner to analyse how people use our site, such that we can improve our service.  
13.2. Cookies  
We may from time to time use cookies on our website. Cookies are very small files which a website uses to identify you when you come back to the site and to store details about your use of the site. Cookies are not malicious programs that access or damage your computer. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but you can choose to reject cookies by changing your browser settings. However, this may prevent you from taking full advantage of our website. Our website may from time to time use cookies to analyses website traffic and help us provide a better website visitor experience. In addition, cookies may be used to serve relevant ads to website visitors through third-party services such as Google AdWords. These ads may appear on this website or other websites you visit.

13.3. Third party sites  
Our site may from time to time have links to other websites not owned or controlled by us. These links are meant for your convenience only. Links to third party websites do not constitute sponsorship or endorsement or approval of these websites. Please be aware that FatForWeightLoss is not responsible for the privacy practises of other such websites. We encourage our users to be aware, when they leave our website, to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personal id
